没搞错吧？
Are you kidding me?
乔伊？
Joey?
乔伊？乔伊…
Joey? Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey!
乔伊 乔伊…
Joey. Joey. Joey.
乔伊
Joey, Joey!
耶
Yeah.
喔 我吵醒你了？
Oh. Oh, did I wake you?
阿甘 再给我一杯咖啡
Gunther, could I get another cup of coffee?
你不卖咖啡时都做什么？
So, uh, what do you do when you're not working here?
- 你不必找话讲   - 好 谢了
- You don't need to fill these silences.     - Okay, thanks.
钱德 你喝第四杯了
Chandler, that's your fourth cup of coffee.
我拼命喝咖啡 是因为我累毙了 因为乔伊开始打呼
I'm drinking lots because I'm exhausted because Joey started snoring.
他睡在隔壁 有那么大声吗？
He's in a different room. He's that loud?
你应该来听听
Oh, you should hear me.
你还得意 你得去睡眠诊所
It's not something to be proud of. Go to a sleep clinic.
我说过 我哪里都不去
I told you, I'm not going to any clinic.
我没问题 是你有问题
I don't have a problem. You're the one with the problem.
你该去"少任性别管我"诊所
You should go to a "Quit-being- a-baby-and-leave-me-alone" clinic.
- 没有那种诊所   - 当然有
- They don't have those.     - Yeah, they do.
少任性别管我
Quit being a baby and leave me alone!
这就是第一课
There, you just had your first class.
我跟一个浅眠的人交往过
I used to go out with this guy that was a light sleeper.
每次我打呼 他就把我翻过去
And whenever I'd snore, he'd roll me over...
他就帮我翻身 打呼就会停
He'd roll me over, and I'd stop snoring.
下次你打呼 我要把你翻过去
Next time you snore, I'm rolling you over!
我忙我的 你玩你的
I gotta do what I gotta do. You gotta do what you gotta do.
奥运主题曲
Oh, the Olympics!
- 大喜之日定了吗？ - 还没
- Have you picked a date?     - Huh? Oh.
没有
No. Not yet.
我还是不敢相信你订婚了
I still can not believe you're engaged.
因为太快了 我不是说你没行情
Just because it's happening so fast. Not because you're a loser.
谢谢 有人看到瑞秋吗？
Thanks. Uh, has anyone seen Rach?
她在楼上"不"洗碗
Mm, she's upstairs not doing the dishes.
这次我绝不妥协
And I'll tell you, I'm not doing them this time.
就算碗盘堆到长了…
I don't care if those dishes sit until they're covered...
我回家就洗
I'll do them when I get home.
对了
Yeah. Oh, hey.
艾蜜莉在伦敦看中一件婚纱
Um, Emily found this wedding dress in London...
- 这么快？ - 对 但尺寸不合
- Already?     - Yeah, but it didn't fit.
很幸运是 这里有家店还有一件她的尺码
Luckily, there's a store here with one left in her size.
但新郎不能看到…
But I'm the groom...
- 我去帮你拿   - 谢谢
- I'll pick it up for you.     - Thank you.
她让你跑腿 帮她拿婚纱
She's got you running errands, picking up wedding dresses...
哗啪
Ha-ha-ha. Wah-pah!
什么是"哗啪"？
What's "wah-pah"?
鞭打啊
You know. Whipped.
哗啪
Wah-pah!
那才不是鞭打 鞭打是…
That's not whipped. Whipped is:
没错啊
That's what I did.
哗啪
Wah-pah!
你什么都不会
You can't do anything!
摩妮卡
Hey, Mon.
- 我正在洗碗   - 嘿
- I was just doing these dishes. Oh...     - Hey.
嘿 你有空吗？
Hi. Do you, uh, have a minute?
有 反正我正打算休息
Yeah, I was just about to take a break anyway.
是这样的…
So listen, uh...
我们还没有机会谈过
...I know you and I haven't had a chance to talk...
自从艾蜜莉和我决定结婚后
...since, uh, Emily and I decided to get married.
我想知道你好不好
And I was just wondering how you were.
如果是你要结婚 我会觉得有点…
If you were getting married, heh, I would feel kind of...
- 你懂吗？ - 懂
- You know?     - Yeah, yeah.
我的确吓了一跳 不过…
It def... Uh, it definitely took me by surprise. But, you know...
我很好
...uh, I'm okay.
- 是吗？ - 对
- Yeah?     - Yeah.
我只是想问下
I just wanted to check.
你真好 谢谢
Oh, that's sweet. Thank you. Oh, ha, ha.
你真好
You're great.
有一天你也会找到真命天子
And I know someday this will happen for you too.
撑着点
You just hang in there.
"撑着点"？
"Hang in there"?
我的意思不是…
Oh, no, I didn't mean...
你没听过一段认真的恋情 叫"我与约书亚"吗？
You haven't heard of a serious relationship called "me and Joshua"?
你们不是才约会四次
Oh. I thought you had just been on four dates.
我不知道你们开始认真了
I didn't realize that had become anything.
我知道 我们是认真了
Oh, yeah. Oh, no, it has become.
那四次约会棒到不行
Yeah. Oh, no, those were four great dates.
- 真的么？ - 是的
- Oh. Yeah?     - Oh, yeah.
我们好契合
I mean, and the connection! I mean, you know.
情感上 心灵上…
Emotionally, mentally. You know?
肉体上
Physically.
- 太好了   - 可不是吗？
- Wow. That's incredible.     - I know, isn't it?
我跟约书亚在一起 你跟艾蜜莉在一起
I'm right there with Joshua. You are right there with Emily.
就像… 大家平手
And it's kind of like it's a tie.
我得继续洗碗了
I gotta get back to my dishes.
我得回去上班了
I gotta get to work.
有个做法会让我很开心
You know what would make me happy?
什么做法？
Oh, yeah, no, what's that?
就是我们四个聚一聚
If the four of us could all, you know, hang out together.
艾蜜莉周末要来
Emily's coming into town this weekend.
要不要星期天一起吃饭？
Why don't, uh, we all have dinner Sunday night?
太好了 是吗？
- That would be great!     - Yeah?
- 那就这么说定了   - 好的
- All right. It's a date!     - Right. Yeah.
"撑着点" 你才撑着点
"Hang in there." You hang in there.
- 你说什么？ - 没有 我在唱歌
- Did you say something?     - No, just singing.
天哪
Oh, my God!
你看这件
Oh, look at this one!
- 好美喔   - 对
- It's so beautiful.     - Yeah. Oof.
这里有一半最后会离婚
About half of these will end up getting divorced.
有什么事吗？
May I help you ladies?
我来拿请你们保留的婚纱
Yes, um, I'm here to pick up a dress on hold.
姓名呢？
What's the name?
- 艾蜜莉华森   - 有 已经准备好了
- Emily Waltham.     - Oh, yes, I have it right here.
你要试穿吗 华森小姐？
Would you like to try it on, Miss Waltham?
你是我见过最美的新娘
You're the most beautiful bride I've ever seen.
可不是吗？
I am, aren't I?
华森小姐
Miss Waltham?
- 是？ - 我们要打烊了
- Yes?     - We're closing.
好吧
All right.
请把戒指还给我
And could I get my ring back?
兄弟 该翻身了
All right, buddy. Time to roll over.
不 不 不…
No, no! No, no, no, no, no!
你一定要去医院 你要去医院…
You are going to a clinic! You're going to a clinic!
还有睡衣店
And a pajama store!
她有用杯子吗？
Does she use the cups?
有 她有用
Yes, I believe she does.
她有用盘子吗？有 她有用
Does she use the plates? Yes, I believe she does!
谢谢
Thank you. Heh.
啊
Aw.
谢谢你
Thank you very much.
谢谢你来
Oh, thank you for coming.
- 等下   - 不行 让我进去
- Uh, just a second.     - No, no! Let me in!
- 菲比？ - 对
- Phoebe?     - Yeah?
- 等一下好吗？ - 不行
- Can you hold on a minute?     - No!
现在就让我进去
You have to let me in right now!
- 只有你吗？ - 对
- Are you alone?     - Yes!
好吧
All right.
讨厌
This sucks.
我不知道就医前一晚不能睡
I have to stay up all night before I go to the stupid clinic.
我好累
I'm so tired.
现在才六点
It's 6:00.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
听说你和约书亚 要和罗斯他们吃饭
I hear you and Joshua are going out with Ross and Emily.
这么做很有风度
And I think... I think that's really cool.
是啊 你处理得很好
Yeah, I think you're handling that really well.
"处理"？
"Handling it"?
没什么好处理的
What do you mean? There's nothing to handle.
如果没有约书亚 我或许会无法接受
Maybe I'd have a problem with this if it wasn't for me and Joshua.
- 反正他们也结不成婚   - 什么？
- They're not gonna get married anyway.     - What?
拜托 他们太急太可笑了
Come on. They rushed into this thing so fast, it's ridiculous!
他们会先订婚个1年
They'll be engaged for like what? A year?
总会有人想通…
Somewhere, one of them is gonna realize what they've done...
取消婚约
...and call the thing off.
你们会先在我的婚礼上跳舞
You'll be dancing at my wedding before you dance at theirs.
我参加婚礼从不跳舞
You know, I don't dance at weddings.
- 为什么？ - 婚礼是认识女生的好地方
- Why not?      - Weddings are a great place to meet women.
而我跳舞是这副德性
When I dance, I look like this.
- 你好   - 嘿
- Hey, man.     - Hey.
四星期后的今天你们有事吗？
So, what are you guys doing four weeks from today?
- 没事   - 没事
- Nothing.     - Nothing.
我…
I am...
有空
...free.
太好了 因为艾蜜莉和我 一个月后要结婚
Great, because we're getting married in a month.
- 什么？ - 没错
- What?     - Yup.
- 一个月后？ - 对
- In a month?     - Yeah.
- 你是说30天后？ - 对
- You mean 30 days?     - Yeah.
- 从今天算起？ - 对
- From now?     - Yeah.
- 太棒了   - 对
- That's great!     - Yeah, ha, ha.
她一直想跟她父母 在同一个地方结婚
Emily always wanted to get married in this place her parents got married...
但那里要拆了 所以…
...but it's gonna be torn down, so...
我知道很疯狂 但从头到尾都很疯狂
I know it's crazy, but everything's been so crazy...
感觉就是很对
...and it just feels right, you know?
那是我经期的第二天
Hey, that's the day after I start menstruating!
这不是我的
This isn't mine.
- 哦   - 嘿 瑞秋
- Ahem     - Hey, Rachel.
嗨
Hi.
- 你好吗？ - 噢 还好
- What's up?     - Oh, heh.
你电话里的声音好尖
Your voice sounded all squeaky on the phone.
没事 我只是想见你
Oh, nothing. I just wanted to see you.
见你 抱你
See you and hug you.
见你
Ha, ha. See you, heh.
- 真好   - 是的
- Great.     - Yeah!
你还好吗？
You okay?
好得不得了 我非常非常高兴
I'm more than okay. I am really, really happy.
你想知道为什么吗？
Want to know why?
我想吗？
Do I?
因为我对我们的关系很满意
Because I am really happy about us.
我觉得我们进展得很好
I think we are so on the right track.
我们很顺利 我们很合
I think we are working. I think we are clicking.
- 你懂吗？ - 当然
- You know?     - Yeah, sure, sure.
- 我们很合   - 是的
- We're... We're clicking.     - Yeah.
如果说有什么小缺憾需要加强
If there was just one little area...
应该就是我们…
...where I think we need to work on, I would think...
不够疯狂
...it's that we're just not crazy enough.
老实说 我不太同意
I got to say, I'm not too sure I agree with that.
你说得对
Well, yeah. You know, yeah, you're right.
我们也很开心
I mean, we have our fun. Yeah?
但是…
But, uh...
我是说很疯狂 你懂吗？
We ju... I mean, like crazy! You know?
好
Okay. All right.
这件事听起来会有点仓卒
This is going to sound, you know, a little, um, hasty.
但你就听吧
But, uh, just go with me.
我们结婚如何？
What if we got married?
- 什么？ - 我知道 你会觉得…
- What?     - Oh, I know. It's so totally like:
"哇 我们行吗？"
"Whoa, can we do this?" You know? I mean...
但感觉很对 你不觉得吗？
But it just feels right. Don't you think? It does.
感觉真的很对 你不…
I mean, it just feels right. Don't you...?
瑞秋
Rachel, um...
你是个…
...you're...
很特别
...a real...
的女性
...special lady.
但我的离婚还没办完
But my divorce isn't final yet...
我们又只约过四次会
...and we've been on four dates.
所以我是想说… 不要
So I'm thinking no...
不过…
...but...
谢了
...thanks.
你这个白痴
You idiot!
- 姓名   - 乔伊崔比亚尼
- Your name, please?     - Joey Tribbiani.
你是否整夜没睡准备接受诊疗
Mm-hm. Did you stay up all night in preparation for your study?
先生？
Uh, sir?
是的
Yes, he did.
好的 待会再叫您
All right. We'll call you in a few minutes.
你看那个女生好辣
Check out that girl. She is really hot.
是啊
Yeah, she is.
你好吗？
How you doing?
- 怎样？ - 你在跟所有病人搭讪
- What?     - You're coming on to the entire room.
- 我是钱德   - 我是玛乔莉
- I'm Chandler. Hi.     - I'm Marjorie. Hi.
- 我可以坐吗？ - 请便
- Do you mind if I sit?     - No, please.
你怎么会来？
So, uh, what are you in for?
我会说梦话
I talk in my sleep.
真巧 我专听梦话
What a coincidence. I listen in my sleep.
给个电话嘛
So why don't you give me your number?
- 准备好了吗？ - 好了
- Are you ready? Okay.     - Yeah.
我接到了
I got it! Mine! Aah!
- 恭喜你   - 谢谢
- Congratulations!     - Thank you! Ha-ha-ha.
- 换我换我   - 好
- Okay, my turn, my turn!     - Okay!
好了吗？
Okay, ready?
好
Okay.
你扔得好烂
That was a terrible throw!
我才不直接扔给你 太假了
I won't throw it right to you. That's not real.
你看我 我还担心太假吗？
Look at me. My big concern is what's real?
天哪
Oh, my God.
我们真的很可悲 对吧？
We're really sad, aren't we?
没错
Yeah, I think we are.
这还不是我的婚纱
This isn't even my dress.
至少不是去"补票婚纱"租的
At least you didn't rent yours from a store called "It's Not Too Late."
我要换掉了 我也是
- I'm changing out of this.     - Me too.
半小时后？我也是
- In, like, a half an hour?     - Me too.
- 这次直接扔给我   - 好
- All right, now throw it straight this time.     - Okay.
我要结婚了
I'm getting married next!
我现在好讨厌普通衣服
I hate my regular clothes now.
低头一看就知道
You know? I look down and I know...
今天不是我人生最特别的日子
...this isn't gonna be the most special day of my life.
一开始是蛮好玩的
Yeah. I mean, it was kind of fun for a while...
但是你不觉得有点蠢？
...but didn't you feel kind of silly?
是有点
I guess.
天哪
Oh, my God!
你好奸诈
Oh, you're such a cheater!
小可爱们
Hello, little ones.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 乔伊会停止打鼾吗？ - 会的
- So is Joey going to stop snoring?     - Yep!
而且有个美女答应跟我约会
And a beautiful woman agreed to go out with me.
乔伊本来想把她 但她选了我
Joey wanted to ask her out, but, uh, you know, she picked me.
怎么会？
How'd that happen?
因为我比较酷
Because I'm cooler.
不 说真的
No, seriously.
她是那种… 乔伊睡死了
She's the kind of girl... Joey was unconscious.
你们好吗？
Hey, you guys! What's happening?
天哪
Oh, my God.
- 那是什么？ - 这是睡眠诊所给的
- What is that?     - Oh! They gave it to me at the sleep clinic.
可以让我不打呼
And it's going to help me not to snore.
你现在在睡觉吗？
Well, are you asleep right now, Joe?
没睡觉应该不用咬
You don't have to wear it unless you are.
我当然知道
I know I don't have to.
它的味道不错
It tastes good.
而且看起来很酷
Plus, you look cool.
我刚打给约书亚
Well, I just called Joshua.
讲得怎样？
Oh, how'd it go?
我尽可能告诉他
I did my best to convince him that I'm not...
我不是想婚想昏头的疯婆子
...some crazy girl who is dying to get married.
- 我只是情绪低落   - 他怎么说？
- And I'm going through a hard time.     - What'd he say?
他的答录机很能体谅
Well, uh, his answering machine was very understanding.
我好沮丧
I feel blue. Ugh.
他一定会再找你的
I bet you anything he'll call you again.
或许吧 但我不认为我在乎
Yeah, maybe. But, you know, I don't think I even care.
我不认为让我难过的是他
I don't think he's the one I'm sad about.
我知道我说我不在意罗斯结婚
I know I said I'm totally okay with Ross getting married.
但是实际上…
But as it turns out...
我调适得并不好
...I don't think I'm handling it all that well.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
我正在思考为什么
And I'm just trying to figure out why.
有想到吗？
Any luck?
罗斯和我不是一直…
Well, yeah. You know how Ross and I have always been...
分分合合？
...on-again, off-again, on-again, off-again?
我想我一直觉得在将来
I guess I just figured, somewhere down the road...
我们会再合…
...we would be on-again.
再分
Again.
我们都这么觉得
You know what? I think we all did.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
嘿
Hey.
我订了星期天晚上的餐厅
I got us reservations for Sunday night.
厄尼之家九点行吗？
How about Ernie's at 9:00?
你得改成三个
Yeah, well, you, uh, better make it for three.
下午三点应该不会饿吧
See, I don't know if we're going to be hungry at 3:00.
是三个人
Three people.
约书亚不会去
Joshua's not going to be there.
- 怎么了？ - 他应该是跟我分手了
- What happened?     - Um, well, I think he broke up with me.
天哪 为什么？
No. Why?
他显然易受惊吓
Apparently, he scares easy.
我很遗憾
Rachel, I'm sorry.
没关系
Eh, it's okay.
人生不如意事十常八九
Sometimes things don't work out the way you thought they would.
过来
Come here.
你不用去接艾蜜莉吗？要
Oh, hey, don't you have to go pick up Emily?
- 你还好吗？ - 很好
- Are you okay?     - Yeah.
我有我的姊妹们
I got my girls.
好
Okay.
你知道怎样会比较开心？
Hey, you know what might cheer you up?
怎样？
What?
说实话
I got to tell you...
我的心情真的好多了
...this really does put me in a better mood.
真希望有整天穿婚纱的工作
Ah, I wish there was a job where I could wear this all the time.
也许以后会有
Maybe someday there will be.
完了 是钱德来借晚上约会的蜡烛
Oh, God, that's Chandler coming by to borrow candles for his big date.
瑞秋 别开门 他会看见
No, Rachel, don't get it! He'll see us!
新郎不能看见新娘
No, yeah! The groom cannot see the bride.
我又不嫁钱德
I'm not going to marry Chandler.
被看到就得嫁了
Not after this!
放轻松就对了
Okay guys, just relax.
我愿意…
I do!
- 我得走了   - 我的天 约书亚…
- I gotta go.     - Wait, Joshua!
这次真的莎哟娜啦了
Yeah, well, that ought to do it.
吃的在这里 很好
Food's here. Fair enough.
还有15分钟
Fifteen-minute warning.
迟了
Late.
大哥 我想睡觉
Dude, I am trying to sleep!